turn off oven
turn off stove
put colander in sink
pick up pot
pour pot into colander
put lid on pot
put pot on stove
take off lid
put lid on stove
pick up colander
pour put colander on pot
pick up chopping block
put down chopping block
open cupboards
close cupboards
pick up bowl
put down bowls
open oven
put on oven gloves
take out fish cakes
pick up fork
push fish cake into bowl
put tray back in oven
Close oven.
Put away oven gloves.
Pick up pot.
Pick up colander.
Put leeks into bowl.
Put vegetables into bowl.
Scrape out colander.
Put down colander.
Put down fork.
Pick up fork.
put fork in bowl
open cupboards
take out soy sauce
take out chili oil
squirt chili oil
put down chili oil
pick up soy sauce
pour on soy sauce
put down soy sauce
pick up tissue
wipe down soy sauce
Pick up colander
Rinse colander
Scrub colander
Put soap on sponge
Rinse colander
Put colander away
Pick up pan
Empty
Rinse pot
Scrub pot
Rinse off pot
Put pot on stove
Shake off hands
[END SUBTITLE]